// This is an array of objects that contains the quiz questions and their options
export const Questions = [
    {
        prompt: "Q.Who was the inventor of Radar?",
        optionA: "Austin",
        optionB: "Bush Wall",
        optionC: "Fleming",
        optionD: "Robert Watson",
        answer: "D",
    },
    {
        prompt: "Q.Solar radiation is measured by",
        optionA: "Astrometer",
        optionB: "Barometer",
        optionC: "Pyrometer",
        optionD: "Manometer",
        answer: "C",
    },
    {
        prompt: "Q.Curie is the unit of",
        optionA: "Temperature",
        optionB: "Radio Activity",
        optionC: "Energy",
        optionD: "Heat",
        answer: "B",
    },
    {
        prompt: "Q.Which one of the following is not an amorphous substance?",
        optionA: "Rubber",
        optionB: "Glass",
        optionC: "Polymer",
        optionD: "Copper",
        answer: "D",
    },
    {
        prompt: "Q. Who is the creator of the World Wide Web?",
        optionA: "Steve Jobs",
        optionB: "Bill Gates",
        optionC: "Tim Berners-Lee",
        optionD: "Larry Page",
        answer: "C",
    },
    {
        prompt: "Q. What is the smallest country in the world by land area?",
        optionA: "Vatican City",
        optionB: "Monaco",
        optionC: "Nauru",
        optionD: "Tuvalu",
        answer: "A",
    },
    {
        prompt: "Q. Who painted the famous artwork 'The Starry Night'?",
        optionA: "Vincent van Gogh",
        optionB: "Leonardo da Vinci",
        optionC: "Pablo Picasso",
        optionD: "Claude Monet",
        answer: "A",
    },
    {
        prompt: "Q. What is the capital city of Australia?",
        optionA: "Sydney",
        optionB: "Melbourne",
        optionC: "Brisbane",
        optionD: "Canberra",
        answer: "D",
    },
    {
        prompt: "Q. What is the largest planet in our solar system?",
        optionA: "Jupiter",
        optionB: "Saturn",
        optionC: "Neptune",
        optionD: "Mars",
        answer: "A",
    },
    {
        prompt: "Q. Who wrote the famous novel 'To Kill a Mockingbird'?",
        optionA: "J.D. Salinger",
        optionB: "Ernest Hemingway",
        optionC: "Harper Lee",
        optionD: "F. Scott Fitzgerald",
        answer: "C",
    },
];
